In my mind, what I want more than anything is 25 years from now, on Thanksgiving, I want my kids to be able to come to our house for Thanksgiving with their wives, girlfriends, baby moms, estranged, whatever, whoever they love, boyfriends, whatever they love, non-binaries, whoever you like.
It's the baby mama, though.
Bring them to the house.
You don't know.
Hey, people make choices.
Listen, paths are not as straight as you.
That's true.
That's kind of like the easing in.
Yeah.
Whoever you wear at the moment, y'all want some greens?
Come on in.
You're all welcome.
Why it's important for me to know that that's what I want, then it helps me inform what I want to do now.
That's good.
Because what will happen is.